newsbycompany.com 2012-10-16

# PRIVACY POLICY www.newsbyco.com

At NewsByCompany.com, we are sensitive about how we deal with information we receive from you. This policy covers how NewsByCompany.com treats personal information that we collect and receive from you, including information related to your past use of NewsByCompany.com products and services. We understand you may not want everyone in the world to have the information you share and that is why we give you control of your information. You choose what information you put in your profile, including contact and personal information, pictures, interests and communities you join. In addition, you control with whom you share that information through the settings on the My Account section.

However, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that user content you post on the site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site.

Whenever you visit or decide to open an account with NewsByCompany.com, you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose and Website use information collected by us as you interact with our Website.

**Personal Information Uses**

NewsByCompany.com asks personal information when you create a membership account with us, such as your name, your e-mail address and any other personal or preference information that you may like.

**E-Mail Address:** We hate spam. We will never sell or rent your e-mail address to any third parties. Your e-mail address will never be displayed anywhere on NewsByCompany.com. It is used only for logistical purposes such as sending you a message, important notices etc.

**Information that we collect**

When you enter NewsByCompany.com, we collect your IP address. This website use information is gathered for all visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using “cookies”. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive

**Cookies:** You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use NewsByCompany.com products or take full advantage of the NewsByCompany.com service. NewsByCompany.com uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to: Access your information when you "sign in"; keep track of preferences you specify while you are using NewsByCompany.com services; display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your interests and activity on NewsByCompany.com; estimate and report our total audience size and traffic; conduct research to improve NewsByCompany.com content and services. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

**Use of information**

When you use NewsByCompany.com, you may send messages, perform searches and queries, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features like informing you of new members, messages, or other information, such as invitations to join friends' networks etc. We also use this information to estimate the total number of users visiting NewsByCompany.com from specific geographical regions.

We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to legal requests, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith/belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the NewsByCompany.com service or using the NewsByCompany.com name. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

**Your choices**

**Choice/Opt-out:** If you no longer wish to receive service communications from us, you are free to opt out from receiving them by e-mailing us at <http://newsbycompany.com/page/ContactUs/>.

You can terminate your account at any time. If you terminate your account, your profile, including any messages in your inbox, will be removed from the site and deleted from NewsByCompany.com servers. Because of the way we maintain this service, such deletion may not be immediate, and residual copies of your profile information may remain on backup media.

**Warning**

Those members that ignore our rules will be banned and/or deleted from our website. NewsByCompany.com reserves the right to delete any image, rating, comment or user account without notice. We also reserve the right to ban any member from any area of our website or the entire site.

NewsByCompany.com may update this policy at any time for any reason. If there are any significant changes to how we handle personal information, we will send a notice to the primary e-mail address specified in your NewsByCompany.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
